Michael Njolomba

+260977308406 michaelnjolomba@gmail.com

Senior Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.



Experience

09/2018 to 05/2021

Web Developer - 09/2018 to 05/2021 Luna Web Design, Lusaka

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

09/2017 to 09/2020

Sales Assistant

Kondwa Lodge, Chongwe.

- Promptly served all alcoholic drinks to guests.
- Maintain stock levels to prevent shortages.
- Strictly abided by all state liquor regulations, particularly in regard to intoxicated persons and minors.
- Participate in bar contests to drive sales and promote the venue.
- Taking care of your appearance (cleanliness, neatness, elegance).

Highlights

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative

Service-focused

- Ability to motivate staff and maintain good relations
- Resistance to stress
- Good manners

Education

Bachelor of Science:
Computer Science- 2021
Mulungushi

University, Kabwe.

Form Five Certificate:
2020,
Mwavi Secondary School
Board.

Hobbies

Playing chess